[rock music]
[摇滚音乐]
- Camp Bear Claw, here we come!
我们要去熊爪营地了！
Ribbit. Ribbit.
呱呱。
What sound is that?
那是什么声音？
- The sound a bear makes.
熊发出的声音。
Duh.
废话。
No, a bear goes grrr.
不，熊是发出'咕噜咕噜'声。
Yeah, if the bear sounds like an elephant.
是啊，如果那熊听起来像大象的话。
- Gee, I swear my bag wasn't this heavy last night.
哎呀，我发誓昨晚我的包没这么重。
Aw, chicks. Always over-packing.
哎，女生们。总是带太多东西。
[laughter]
[笑声]
Wait a minute.
等一下。
What's this astronomy book doing in my bag?
这本天文学书怎么会在我包里？
Ricky?
瑞奇？
I have a perfectly good explanation.
我有一个完美的解释。
I ran out of room in mine. That is all.
我的包里没地方了。仅此而已。
Ugh!
呃！
And what's this?
这是什么？
"Rugged Mud?"
"耐磨泥？"
Careful. That's my jar of dirt.
小心点。那是我的泥土罐。
I'm pretty sure they have dirt at camp.
我敢肯定营地里也有泥土。
But this stuff is pure.
但这东西是纯的。
It's never been on the ground.
它从未接触过地面。
It's going from this jar to my face.
它直接从这罐子到我脸上。
Why would you want to look dirty?
你为什么要看起来脏兮兮的？
'Cause girls dig rugged dudes.
因为女孩们喜欢粗犷的男生。
The dirtier the flirtier.
越脏越迷人。
Nicky, you're already wearing a first-aid kit.
尼基，你已经戴着急救包了。
Yeah, and that's my second-aid kit. Ow.
是啊，那是我第二个急救包。哎哟。
The only thing of mine you guys left in my bag is one shoe.
你们留在我包里的唯一东西就是一只鞋。
How am I supposed to flip without a flop?
没有拖鞋我怎么拍?
Well, it can't be done,
嗯，那没办法了,
which means now there's more room for my underwear.
也就是说现在我的内衣有更多空间了。
- No way.
——不行。
You didn't pack underwear?
你没带内裤吗？
I was just gonna wear yours.
我打算穿你的。
- You're not wearing mine. - Or mine.
——你别想穿我的。——也不穿我的。
Fine.
好吧。
Dawn?
道恩？
All right. I guess another two more weeks
好吧，我想再穿两周
in these won't matter.
再过两周这些就不重要了。
Ugh. Camp is supposed to be fun.
呃。夏令营应该是好玩的。
I can't believe I have to spend it with you three.
真不敢相信我得和你们三个一起过。
You know what? I am this close to just staying home.
你知道吗？我差点就想待在家里了。
- Yeah. - You might as well. - Maybe you guys should stay home!
- 对啊。 - 你干脆就别去了。 - 或许你们应该待在家里！
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇，哇！
No one is staying home except me and your mother.
除了我和你妈妈，谁也不许待在家里。
This is why camp will be good for you.
这就是为什么夏令营对你们有好处。
You'll be outside, meet new people, do new things.
你们会在户外，认识新朋友，尝试新事物。
You'll hardly know each other is there.
你们几乎不会注意到对方的存在。
Okay, let's, uh, start loading up the car.
好吧，我们开始往车上装东西吧。
- Load it up. - Okay.
— 装车吧。— 好的。
Got it. Got it.
知道了。知道了。
You know what? Maybe Mom's right.
你知道吗？也许妈妈是对的。
Maybe we don't need to know each other at all.
也许我们根本不需要了解对方。
If no one knows us, no one will know we're related.
如果没人认识我们，就不会有人知道我们是亲戚。
That's perfect!
太完美了！
And I can finally see what being like an only child is like.
我终于可以体验一下独生子女的感觉了。
So it's agreed. When we get to camp, we're not related.
就这么定了。到了营地，我们就不认亲戚了。
Good idea.
好主意。
Should we quaddle up?
我们应该搭伙吗？
Why would we quaddle up if we don't know each other?
如果我们互不相识，为什么要搭伙呢？
Yeah, we do.
是的，我们认识。
That's Ricky. That's Nicky, and--
那是里基。那是尼基，还有——
Oh, we already started.
哦，我们已经开始了。
Good work, strangers.
干得好，陌生人。
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
[whistling melody]
[吹口哨的旋律]
♪ ♪
[rhythmic clapping] ♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
♪ ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na-na, hey! ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐，嘿！ ♪
- ♪ One, two ♪ - ♪ Na na na na na-na ♪
- ♪ 一、二 ♪ - ♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ One, two, three, four! ♪
♪ 一、二、三、四！ ♪
[woman over loudspeaker] Hey, camper bears!
[女声通过扩音器] 嘿，露营的小熊们！
Please check in at the front desk
请在前台登记
and have a bear-y good day!
并祝你们有一个非常愉快的一天！
- Welcome to Camp Bear Claw.
欢迎来到熊爪营地。
Grrrr.
吼。
Names?
名字？
- Dawn Harper. - Ricky Harper.
- 道恩·哈珀。 - 里基·哈珀。
- Dicky Harper. - Nicky Harper.
- 迪基·哈珀。 - 尼基·哈珀。
[all] No relation.
[所有人] 没有关系。
Whatever.
无所谓。
Uh, here are your bunk assignments.
呃，这是你们的铺位分配。
Now go and have the adventure of a lifetime.
现在去体验一生的冒险吧。
Grrrr.
吼。
Guys, it worked!
伙计们，成功了！
For the first time in our lives, we're not related.
这是我们生命中第一次，我们不再有血缘关系。
We're not quads. We're just kids.
我们不再是四胞胎。我们只是普通的孩子。
[all] We're free!
[所有人] 我们自由了！
I hope Mom and Dad don't miss us too much.
希望爸爸妈妈不要太想念我们。
[both] We're free!
[两人] 我们自由了！
[laughing] [dog barking]
[笑声] [狗叫声]
Okay, campers, now that you've got your scheduled activities,
好了，营员们，既然你们有了安排的活动，
go out there and have a great day!
出去享受美好的一天吧！
Hey, you guys must be my cabinmates.
嘿，你们一定是我的室友。
I'm Dawn, only child,
我是Dawn，独生子女，
as in absolutely no brothers.
就像，绝对没有兄弟。
- I'm Sienna. - I'm McKenna.
- 我是Sienna。 - 我是McKenna。
And I'm Jenna.
我是Jenna。
[all] We're the Ennas.
我们都是Ennas。
Okay, so, uh, what are you guys psyched for?
好吧，那么，呃，你们对什么感到兴奋？
Archery? Capture the Flag?
射箭？夺旗？
[gasps] Trust falls?
信任坠落？
Here I go!
我来了！
[thud]
砰！
Okay, that was fun.
好吧，那很有趣。
You know, we got some room to grow. But what do you want to do now?
你知道，我们还有很大的成长空间。但现在你想做什么？
What we always do-- talk about boys!
我们总是做的——聊聊男生！
Yeah, boys are cool,
是啊，男生很酷，
but have you guys seen the volleyball court?
但你们有没有看到排球场？
Speaking of boys, did you see Jake?
说到男生，你看到Jake了吗？
He got braces with green brackets
他戴了绿色支架的牙套
which totally match his eyes.
完全和他的眼睛颜色相配。
Uh, speaking of eyes,
呃，说到眼睛，
I'm using mine to spy those archery targets over there. Who wants to go?
我正用我的眼睛盯着那边的射箭靶子。谁想去？
Nah. I'd rather get a closer look at Jake.
不了。我宁愿近距离看看Jake。
- Me too. - Boys!
- 我也是。 - 男孩们！
Okay, if you need me, I'll be at archery...
好的，如果你们需要我，我会在射箭场...
by myself...
独自一人...
because I'm free.
因为我自由。
Aah! Spider!
啊！蜘蛛！
Bigger spider!
更大的蜘蛛！
Excuse me. I'm looking for the counselor
劳驾。我在找负责营地安全的辅导员
in charge of camp safety.
是的，那就是我。
Yeah, that'd be me.
你？那个“随便”的家伙？
You? The "whatever" guy?
他们现在就这么叫我吗？
Is that what they're calling me now?
Whatever.
无所谓。
You all want to go rock climbing or something?
你们都想去做攀岩之类的活动吗？
Yes, but first, I've noticed a bunch of hazards around camp
是的，但首先，我注意到营地周围有很多安全隐患
that are preventing me from having fun.
这些让我无法尽情享受。
For example, I'd love to go rock climbing,
比如说，我很想去攀岩，
but this strap is broken.
但这个带子是坏的。
- Um...
呃...
Good to go.
好了，可以了。
- Ow!
哎哟！
- Ahh, this is so great, Tom. - Ha ha!
- 啊，这太棒了，汤姆。 - 哈哈！
- No kids! You know, I can't remember the last time
- 没有孩子！你知道，我都不记得上次
we got to watch a serious movie for serious adults.
我们能看一部真正给成年人看的严肃电影是什么时候了。
Yes! So get ready Chain Saw Leprechaun Two:
是的！准备好《链锯小妖精二：
Attack of the Four Leaf Cleaver.
四叶刀的攻击》。
[imitates knife slashing]
[模仿刀子划过]
[laughs]
[笑]
Here we go.
开始了。
[children shouting playfully on TV]
[电视上孩子们嬉戏的声音]
Oh, no. Oh, no, Anne.
哦，不。哦，不，安妮。
Chain Saw Leprechaun's going to a kids' party.
链锯小妖精要去参加一个儿童派对。
[gasps] This is starting off strong.
[倒吸一口气] 这开头就很劲爆。
No, it's the wrong DVD.
不，放错DVD了。
This is the quad's fifth birthday party.
这是四胞胎的五岁生日派对。
Oh, let's turn it off.
哦，关掉吧。
We're supposed to be in a kid-free zone.
我们应该在一个无儿童区域。
But wait. Wait. Look at their cute little five-year-old faces
但是等等。等等。看看他们那些五岁小脸蛋
all covered in cake.
全都是蛋糕。
Aw.
哎呀。
But you're right, we-- we shouldn't be watching this.
但你说得对，我们——我们不应该看这个。
No, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait!
不，不，等等，等等，等等！
- This is the part where Dicky breaks his animal sounds wheel. - Oh, yeah!
——这是Dicky弄坏动物声音轮的地方。——哦，对！
Oh--All right, here's where he plays with it.
哦——好吧，他在这里玩它。
[man on TV] The frog says, cock-a-doodle-do!
（电视上的男人）青蛙说，喔喔喔！
[Dicky] Look, Mommy, I'm learning.
（Dicky）看，妈妈，我在学习。
Oh, it's so cute the way he used to do the wrong animal sounds.
哦，他以前用错动物声音的样子真可爱。
He must have been so confused when you finally told him.
你最终告诉他时，他一定很困惑。
I thought you told him.
我以为你告诉他了。
No.
没有。
You're Lilly, right? I'm Dicky.
你是Lilly，对吧？我是Dicky。
Rugged only child.
粗犷的独生子。
Raised by wolves. Moooo!
由狼养大。哞！
You know that's a cow, right?
你知道那是牛，对吧？
Well, I don't want to have our first fight,
好吧，我不想我们第一次就吵架，
so let's just "moooove" one.
所以我们就“哞”一声过去吧。
You're so rugged. Look at that dirt.
你真粗犷。看看那泥土。
We don't stand a chance against your muscles.
我们对抗不了你的肌肉。
Let me see you flex those bad boys.
让我看看你展示那些肌肉。
Pull!
拉！
Yes! We win! You "mooze."
耶！我们赢了！你“哞”了。
She's so into me.
她对我太着迷了。
At last we meet, giant telescope.
终于见到你了，巨型望远镜。
And the legends are true!
传说都是真的！
You are real, and you are spectacular.
你是真实存在的，而且非常壮观。
Where do you think you're going, little dipper?
小北斗，你以为你要去哪里？
I just wanted to peak through the largest telescope
我只是想透过这架我有史以来能接触到的最大的望远镜看看。
I've ever had access to.
哇哦。慢着点，斯蒂芬·霍金。
Whoa. Slow your roll, Stephen Gawking.
谁说你能接触到的？
Who says you have access?
好吧，我想我们一开始就没处理好关系。
Okay, I think we got off on the wrong foot.
瑞奇·哈珀，独生子。望远镜只供返营者使用。
Ricky Harper, only child.
瑞奇·哈珀，独生子。
The telescope's for returning campers only.
望远镜只供回营的露营者使用。
So make a U-turnicus, tiny Copernicus.
所以请掉头吧，小哥白尼。
[both laugh]
[两人笑]
Does the fact
我是否理解到足以因此受伤的事实
that I understand that enough to be hurt by it help my case?
有助于我的情况吗？
[woman over loudspeaker] Attention, little bears.
[通过扩音器传来的女性声音] 小熊们请注意。
Campfire s'mores hour has begun.
篝火棉花糖夹心饼干时间开始了。
So grab your chocolate, marshmallows,
带上你的巧克力、棉花糖
and graham crackers.
和全麦饼干。
Oh, hey, Ennas!
哦，嘿，Ennas！
I missed you at canoeing earlier.
我之前在划独木舟时没看到你。
I was the only one in the canoe,
我是独木舟上唯一的人，
so I mostly just paddled in circles.
所以我基本上只是在原地打转。
[laughs] Circles.
（笑）原地打转。
Ooh, check out the new boy over there.
哦，看看那边的新男孩。
He's so rugged.
他看起来很粗犷。
Who, him? He's not rugged at all.
谁，他？他一点也不粗犷。
He's wearing dirt from a jar he brought from home.
他只是穿着他从家里带来的罐子里的泥土。
Wait. How do you know what he brought from home?
等等。你怎么知道他从家里带了什么？
Home? W-who said "home"? I didn't say "home."
家？谁说了“家”？我没说“家”。
Yeah, you did.
是的，你说了。
It's like he's your brother or something.
他就像你兄弟什么的。
Brother? I told you, I'm an only child!
兄弟？我告诉过你，我是独生子！
Then how do you know so much about him?
那你为什么对他这么了解？
Um, because...
嗯，因为...
he's, um...
他，嗯...
Are you crushing on him?
你是不是对他有意思？
Is he your boyfriend?
他是你男朋友吗？
Oh, my gosh, that would be so cool.
哦，天哪，那太酷了。
We would totally do camp activities with you
我们绝对会和你一起做露营活动
if you brought your boyfriend along.
如果你带你的男朋友来。
You would? Why?
真的吗？为什么？
Because even though we talk about boys at camp a lot,
因为虽然我们在露营时经常谈论男孩，
we never actually talk to any of them.
但我们从未真正和任何一个交谈过。
- She's afraid. - So are you!
- 她害怕。 - 你也害怕！
[both] So is he your boyfriend?
[两人] 那他是你的男朋友吗？
Well, the truth is...
嗯，事实是...
Say yes, and we'll go canoeing with you.
说是，我们就和你一起去划独木舟。
Yes, Dicky is my boyfriend!
是的，迪基是我的男朋友！
[Ennas] Yay!
[Ennas] 耶！
[Ennas giggling]
[Ennas 咯咯笑]
OMG, you and Dicky--
天哪，你和Dicky——
biggest camp news ever!
这可是夏令营有史以来最大的新闻！
You know, you know, probably not ever.
你知道，可能没那么夸张。
You know, I'm sure there's been other things.
你知道，我敢肯定还有其他事情。
You know what? Let's talk about it in the canoe.
你知道吗？我们在独木舟上再聊这个吧。
Uh, ca-no. First, introduce us.
呃，独木舟。首先，介绍我们认识。
Oh, I would, but he looks kind of busy.
哦，我会的，但他看起来有点忙。
Even more reason. You don't want Lilly crashing your crush.
正因为如此。你不会想让Lilly打扰你的暗恋吧。
Get in there!
进去吧！
Don't be scared of rattlesnakes.
别怕响尾蛇。
You can always hear them coming by the sound they make.
你总能通过它们发出的声音提前听到它们来。
Baaa. Baaa.
咩。咩。
You know that's a sheep, right?
你知道那是只羊，对吧？
Hey, you! Stay away from my...
嘿，你！离我的……
boyfriend.
男朋友远点。
[both] Boyfriend?
[两人] 男朋友？
Yes, and, uh, these are the Ennas!
是的，而且，呃，这些是恩纳斯一家！
Everybody's met? Great!
大家都见过了？太好了！
- But I'm-- - Excuse us.
- 但我—— - 请让我们过去。
Boyfriend?
男朋友？
Wow. My jar dirt is working too good.
哇，我的罐子里的土效果太好了。
No!
不！
Look, I know this is crazy,
听着，我知道这很疯狂，
but I need you to pretend you're my boyfriend
但我需要你假装是我的男朋友
so these girls will actually do camp stuff with me.
这样这些女孩才会真正和我一起做露营活动。
But I want to do camp stuff with Lilly.
但我想和莉莉一起做露营活动。
Do this for me, and I'll stop kicking you in the shins.
帮我这个忙，我就不再踢你的小腿了。
You're not kicking me in the shins.
你没踢我的小腿。
Ow, ow, ow! Okay, okay, okay, fine!
哎哟，哎哟，哎哟！好吧，好吧，好吧，好吧！
Oh, hey! We're just playing shinsies.
哦，嘿！我们只是在玩踢小腿游戏。
Cute. Let us take your picture,
真可爱。让我们给你拍张照片，
so we can totally post it and tell all our friends
这样我们就可以完全发到网上，告诉所有朋友
we have a friend who has a boyfriend.
我们有个朋友有男朋友了。
Put your arms around each other. It'll look super cute.
互相搭着肩膀。这样看起来超级可爱。
Get closer.
再靠近一点。
Touch cheeks!
脸颊贴脸颊！
[camera shutter clicks]
[相机快门声]
Let's go post it.
我们去发照片吧。
- Oh, come on. - Why would you do this?
哦，拜托。
Trust me, you can do worse.
你为什么要这么做？
[playing harmonica]
相信我，你可以做得更糟。
♪ ♪
Um, Safety Counselor Ty?
呃，安全辅导员泰？
Shouldn't you be tending to that alarmingly large fire?
你不应该去处理那个惊人的大火吗？
Who cares, when the fire in my heart is out forever?
谁在乎呢，当我的心火已经永远熄灭了？
Oh, Daphne!
哦，达芙妮！
[plays harmonica]
Wait. Loudspeaker Daphne dumped you?
等等。广播员达芙妮甩了你？
That's why you don't care about camp safety.
这就是你不在乎营地安全的原因。
You got to snap out of it!
你得振作起来！
[sighs] Man, why should I listen to you?
[叹气] 伙计，我为什么要听你的？
You don't know what it's like to be burned by love.
你不知道被爱情伤害是什么感觉。
If it's anything like being burned
如果那感觉像被
by an out-of-control fire,
失控的火燃烧一样，
we're all about to know what that's like.
我们很快就会知道那是什么感觉了。
[sobbing]
[啜泣]
[playing harmonica off-key]
[用口琴走调地演奏]
Whoa! That new girl Dawn has a boyfriend!
哇！新来的女孩Dawn有男朋友了！
Nah.
不。
Yeah. It's the guy with the long hair.
是的。就是那个长头发的家伙。
Nah.
不。
I think his name is Dicky.
我觉得他叫迪基。
[gasps]
（吸气声）
Nah.
不。
The one who does those wildly inaccurate animal impressions.
就是那个做那些极其不准确的动物模仿的家伙。
No!
不！
There's no way any of that Dawn and Dicky stuff is true.
那些关于道恩和迪基的事绝对不可能是真的。
That's impossible.
那是不可能的。
There's something horribly wrong with these.
这些真是糟糕透顶。
They only see evil!
他们只看到邪恶！
You're just jealous like the rest of us.
你只是像我们其他人一样嫉妒而已。
We all have a crush on Dawn.
我们都对Dawn有点心动。
Hey! If we let that Dicky guy use our telescope,
嘿！如果我们让那个Dicky家伙用我们的望远镜，
do you think he'd bring her?
你觉得他会带她来吗？
Wait a minute. Just because Dawn is his...
等一下。就因为Dawn是他的...
girlfriend, you'd let him use the telescope?
女朋友，你就让他用望远镜？
- Totally. - Yeah.
- 当然。 - 是的。
Someone missing the kids over there?
那边有人想念孩子们吗？
What? Who, me someone? No.
什么？谁，我吗？不。
No, I'm enjoying every second of our kid-free time.
不，我正享受着我们没有孩子的每一秒。
Oh. So all those pancakes are just for the two of us.
哦。这么说那些煎饼只是为我们两个人准备的。
[sighs] Fine. I admit it.
（叹气）好吧。我承认。
I miss those cute little stinkers.
我想念那些可爱的小捣蛋鬼。
Eh, me too.
嗯，我也是。
Why don't we just get out of the house
我们为什么不离开家
and go for a nice drive?
去兜兜风呢？
And visit them?
然后去看他们？
No. There's no parents allowed.
不行。家长不允许进入。
Let's just hop in the minivan and see where the day takes us.
我们就跳上小型货车，看看今天会把我们带到哪里去。
That's so weird.
这太奇怪了。
The day took us to the woods right outside the kids' camp.
今天把我们带到了孩子们营地外的树林里。
[laughs, imitates explosion]
[笑，模仿爆炸声]
Okay, campers, it's time for Extreme Hide-and-Seek.
好了，露营者们，现在是极限捉迷藏的时间。
[all cheering]
[所有人欢呼]
So...
所以...
I heard you and our brother are an item.
我听说你和我们哥哥在一起了。
Shh! It's all pretend to get my cabinmates
嘘！这都是为了让我同屋的人
to do activities with me.
和我一起参加活动而假装出来的。
Camp is finally starting to be fun.
夏令营终于开始变得有趣了。
Well, camp won't be fun for me
嗯，对我来说夏令营不会有趣
till I get to use that telescope.
直到我能使用那台望远镜。
So I'm gonna need you to drop the Dicky
所以我需要你放下迪基
and get with the Ricky.
和里基在一起。
Hey, guys? Are the rumors true?
嘿，伙计们？那些传言是真的吗？
Yes, Dicky is Dawn's boyfriend.
是的，迪基是唐的男朋友。
Whoa!
哇！
I was talking about the camp sunscreen being expired...
我是在说营地的防晒霜过期了...
but this is much more disturbing.
但这更让人不安。
It's all fake, Nicky.
都是假的，Nicky。
Yeah, but she's about to fake break up with him to be with me.
是的，但她打算假装和他分手，然后和我在一起。
Um, no I'm not, Ricky.
呃，不，我不是，Ricky。
I'm perfectly happy in my current fake situation.
我对我现在的假情况感到非常满意。
Ooh, fake breakup.
哦，假分手。
That's how I can get through to Ty.
这样我就能接近Ty了。
This may be playing with fire,
这可能是在玩火，
but it's safer than playing with fire.
但比玩火安全。
So, if anyone asks, you're my ex-girlfriend,
所以，如果有人问起，你是我的前女友，
and you broke my heart.
而且你伤了我的心。
Thanks, sis.
谢谢，姐姐。
There's my boo from cabin two.
那是我在二号小屋的宝贝。
Ew. What happened to your face?
呃。你的脸怎么了？
According to the warning label on my jar of dirt,
根据我那罐泥土上的警告标签，
it's probably a fungus.
可能是真菌。
Is it really noticeable?
真的很明显吗？
Yeah, a little bit.
是的，有一点。
Forget that.
别管那个了。
Lilly saw us making dream catchers,
莉莉看到我们在做捕梦网，
and now she's totally jealous.
现在她完全嫉妒了。
Couple more camp activities together,
再一起参加几次营地活动，
and I can dump you and upgrade to a girl
我就可以甩了你，换个不是我妹妹的女孩。
who's not my sister.
好吧，这是史上最烂的躲藏地点。
Okay, this is the worst hiding spot ever.
营地里最可爱的一对情侣！
There's the cutest couple at camp!
啊！- 真恶心！
- [gasps] Aah! - Nasty!
现在就甩了他！
Dump him now!
狄奇，结束了。不是你的问题，是你的脸。
Dicky, it's over. It's not you. It's your face.
她已经和瑞克斯特在一起了。
She's already moved on to the Rickster.
谁？
Who?
我啦，我是瑞克斯特。我们很幸福。
Me, I'm the Rickster.
我，我是Rickster。
And we're very happy.
我们非常幸福。
Now we know somebody who's had two boyfriends.
现在我们知道有人有两个男朋友了。
Picture!
拍照！
[camera shutter clicks]
（相机快门声）
Ty?
Ty？
Are you slow-dancing with Daphne's microphone
你是在和Daphne的麦克风慢舞
taped to a broom?
绑在扫帚上吗？
No. [laughs] Yeah.
不。[笑] 是的。
No. Yeah.
不。是的。
No, no. [laughs] Maybe.
不，不。[笑]也许。
No. Yeah.
不。是的。
Listen, man, you don't know what it's like
听着，伙计，你不知道那是什么感觉
to be crushed by an angel.
被天使碾压。
You're wrong. I've also been crushed by an angel.
你错了。我也被天使碾压过。
You may know her as... Camper Dawn.
你可能知道她叫...露营者Dawn。
The one that was with Camper Dicky
就是和露营者Dicky在一起
but is now with Camper Ricky?
但现在和露营者Ricky在一起的那个？
She's what?
她怎么了？
No, see, that doesn't even bother me.
不，看，那甚至不会困扰我。
You know how I got over her?
你知道我是怎么忘记她的吗？
I focused on other things...
我把注意力转移到其他事情上……
like camp safety, and you should too.
比如营地安全，你也应该这样做。
Yeah. You know, maybe you're right.
是啊。你知道，也许你是对的。
[sighs] Maybe I should, Camper Nicky,
[叹气]也许我应该，营地尼基，
and just forget about how Daphne
然后忘记达芙妮
was the greatest thing that ever happened to me.
是我经历过的最美好的事。
I was?
我是吗？
Daphne?
达芙妮？
Ty?
泰？
- Daphne. - Oh, Ty.
- Daphne. - 哦，Ty。
Thank you so much.
非常感谢你。
You've made me so happy, and now I'm gonna make you happy.
你让我感到非常幸福，现在我要让你也幸福。
Great. You're gonna start focusing on camp safety?
太好了。你打算开始关注营地的安全吗？
No. I'm gonna get you and Camper Dawn back together.
不。我要让你和露营者Dawn重归于好。
Oh, please don't.
哦，请不要。
[all giggling]
[大家都笑了]
Um, Ricky-pie?
呃，Ricky-pie？
How much longer are you gonna be?
你还要多久？
Patience, Dawny-cakes.
耐心点，Dawny-cakes。
It's still not dark enough
天还不够黑
to see Ursa Major or Cassiopeia.
还看不到大熊座或仙后座。
[Ty on loudspeaker] Camper Dawn, please report to Bear Claw Point.
[Ty通过扩音器] 露营者Dawn，请前往Bear Claw Point报到。
Yes! Cassio-see ya!
太好了！Cassio-再见！
Uh, Nicky, what's going on?
呃，Nicky，发生什么事了？
This might sound strange,
这听起来可能有点奇怪，
but for the safety of everyone at camp,
但为了营地里每个人的安全，
you need to dump Ricky and fake get back together with me.
你需要甩掉Ricky，然后假装和我复合。
They're flowers.
它们是花。
[gasps] Oh, this has to stop!
[倒吸一口气] 哦，这必须停止！
There you are. I need you back.
你在这儿。我需要你回来。
Lilly won't pay attention to me unless I'm hanging out with you.
莉莉不会注意我，除非我和你在一起。
[coughs]
（咳嗽声）
Dawn's already taken...
Dawn已经被……
by the Rickster.
被Rickster带走了。
Who?
谁？
Me, I'm the Rickster.
我，我是Rickster。
No, she's mine.
不，她是我的。
[boys grunting]
（男孩们哼哼声）
Dawn is mine! I need her way more than you do!
Dawn是我的！我比你需要她得多！
Hey, those are my flowers!
嘿，那些是我的花！
[all shouting]
[所有人都在喊]
Where is this camp? Ugh. I hope we're not lost.
这个营地在哪儿？呃。希望我们没有迷路。
Don't worry. I'm leaving a trail of pancakes
别担心。我正在留下一串煎饼
so we can find our way back.
这样我们就能找到回去的路了。
[children arguing]
[孩子们在争吵]
Wait, wait. I hear kids arguing.
等等，等等。我听到孩子们在争吵。
- [gasps] We must be close! - Shh!
- [吸气] 我们一定很接近了！ - 嘘！
Remember, no parents allowed.
记住，不允许家长进入。
So be quiet with your big loud feet.
所以请安静，你的大脚丫太吵了。
Aaah!
啊！
- Are you okay? - Yes. Yeah.
- 你还好吗？ - 是的，还好。
- Okay. - I think I'm okay. - You sure? - Wow.
- 好的。 - 我想我没事。 - 你确定？ - 哇。
Aaaah!
啊！
Oh! Wow! That stick hates me.
哦！哇！那根棍子讨厌我。
Aaah!
啊！
[grunts]
（咕哝声）
Aaah!
啊！
No!
不！
Why do I keep walking into--
为什么我总是撞到——
Aaah!
啊！
No!
不！
Are you doing this on purp--
你是故意这么做的吗——
Aaaah!
啊！
Uh, what was that?
呃，那是什么？
Well, if I've learned anything since my fifth birthday...
好吧，如果我从五岁生日以来学到了什么的话……
[Tom yelling]
[汤姆大喊]
- That's an elephant! - It's a bear!
- 那是一头大象！ - 那是一只熊！
[all] Bear!
[所有人] 熊！
Whatever! Either way, I'm running!
无所谓！反正我得跑了！
[children] Bear!
熊！
Bear? And we have a trail of pancakes leading right to us.
熊？而且我们有一串煎饼直接引向我们。
- Oh, no! Bears love pancakes! - I know!
哦，不！熊喜欢煎饼！我知道！
[screaming]
[尖叫]
Okay, all right, all right, you know what they say.
好吧，好吧，你知道他们怎么说。
The best way to scare off a bear is to act like a bear.
吓跑熊的最好办法就是表现得像熊。
[growling]
[咆哮]
- Guys! Guys, stop! I can't run anymore.
伙计们！伙计们，停下！我跑不动了。
Do any of you know the way back to camp?
你们有人知道回营地的路吗？
[boys] No!
不！
Great. We're lost.
太好了，我们迷路了。
[Tom growling]
汤姆咆哮
I can't believe this is our first camp experience.
我真不敢相信这是我们的第一次露营经历。
I just wanted to do camp stuff and have fun.
我只想做些露营的事情，然后玩得开心。
Me too. I know we all get on each other's nerves sometimes,
我也是。我知道我们有时会互相惹恼，
but I have to admit, camp was hard without you.
但我必须承认，没有你在，露营真的很艰难。
And dangerous!
而且还很危险！
And I wish I packed more underwear.
我希望我多带了些内裤。
None of this would have happened
如果不是我们隐瞒了真相，这一切都不会发生。
if we'd just told the truth.
如果我们当时说了实话就好了。
You know what? I'm proud to say it loud.
你知道吗？我自豪地说出来。
I'm your sister, and you're my brothers!
我是你的妹妹，你们是我的哥哥！
[Ennas] Ewwwww!
哎呀！
[all] Hey, everyone.
大家好。
Uh, so--so your brothers
呃，所以——所以你的哥哥们
are your boyfriends?
是你的男朋友？
It's not what it sounds like.
不是听起来那样的。
Yeah, we're definitely not her brothers.
是的，我们肯定不是她的哥哥。
[growling]
（咆哮声）
[all] Mom? Dad?
[所有人] 妈妈？爸爸？
Oh. This isn't the outlet mall.
哦。这不是奥特莱斯购物中心。
[laughs] You kids know your dad.
[笑] 你们这些孩子了解你们的爸爸。
He never wants to ask for directions.
他从来不想问路。
Hey, hey, where am I?
嘿，嘿，我在哪儿？
So you really are brothers and sister?
所以你们真的是兄弟姐妹？
Yes. These are my brothers.
是的。这些是我的兄弟。
So what do you say?
那你们怎么说？
Can we all just forget that we lied and start over?
我们能不能都忘记我们撒了谎，重新开始？
[all] No.
[所有人] 不行。
Okay, you guys had enough camp for the summer?
好吧，你们这个夏天在营地待够了吗？
- All set. - Let's go.
- 准备好了。 - 走吧。
We'll explain in the car.
我们会在车上解释。
Okay. Follow the pancakes!
好的。跟着煎饼走！
We'll explain in the car.
我们会在车上解释。
[Tom] Hey, where'd all the pancakes go?
嘿，所有的煎饼都去哪儿了？
[bear growls]
（熊的咆哮声）
Elephant!
大象！
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
♪ Na na na na na na na na na na na na ♪
♪ 呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐呐 ♪
[whistling]
[吹口哨]
♪ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah ♪
♪ 耶，耶，耶，耶 ♪
♪ Yeah! ♪
♪ 耶！ ♪